{
    "id": "67680da696ce4bcbae3d5e23dedfb741",
    "title": "Adverb clause exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "dc2f48f4e0d74efdb621ba59c9cfb156",
            "title": "Adverb Clause Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I waited for my friend ......................................... he arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "up to",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He hid ......................................... his pursuers could not find him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "there",
                        "where",
                        "when"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am as intelligent ....................................... you are.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "so",
                        "than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ he was not there, I left a message with his mother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "So",
                        "Therefore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We eat .............................................. we may live.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "so",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ........................................... tired that she could barely stand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................................. you eat too much, you may fall ill.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Whether",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ he started early, he finished late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Though",
                        "So"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................... you do not tell me everything, I will not be able to help you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless",
                        "Whether"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do not go ................................................ I get ready.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "unless",
                        "up to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}